Guide to the Amos Alonzo Stagg Papers 1866-1964
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Football
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Cornell (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Dartmouth (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Eau Clair Normal (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Florida (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Harvard (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Illinois, 1903-1912 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Illinois 1912-1917 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Illinois 1918-1919 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Illinois 1920-1921 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Illinois 1922-1923 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Illinois 1924-1925 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Illinois 1926 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Illinois 1927 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Illinois 1928 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Illinois 1929 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Illinois 1930 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Illinois 1931-1932 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Iowa (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Indiana 1908-1930 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Indiana 1931 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Iowa (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Kansas (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Kentucky (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Maryland (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Michigan 1897-1904 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Michigan 1905 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Michigan 1910-1922 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Michigan 1923-1929 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Michigan 1930 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Michigan 1931 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Michigan 1932 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Minnesota 1899-1909 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Minnesota 1910-1911 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Minnesota 1912-1915 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Minnesota 1916-1925 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Minnesota 1926-1930 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Mississippi (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Missouri (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Monmouth (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - North Central (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Northwestern 1903-1910 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Northwestern 1911-1920 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Northwestern 1921-1924 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Northwestern 1925-1926 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Northwestern 1927-1932 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Notre Dame (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Oklahoma (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Ohio State 1918-1921 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--, Ohio State 1922-1924 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Ohio State 1925-1927 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Pennsylvania 1898-1924 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Pennsylvania 1925-1926 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Pennsylvania 1927-1928 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Princeton (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Purdue 1905-1915 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Purdue 1916-1924 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Purdue 1925-1929 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Purdue 1930 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports - Purdue 1931-1932 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Tennessee (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Texas (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Tulane (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Vanderbilt (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Virginia (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Washington (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports, West Point (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Wisconsin (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - University of Chicago football scouting reports--Yale (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous and unidentifiable scouting reports - Folder 14: Scouting instructions (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1906 [correspondence re] (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1907 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1908 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1909 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1912 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1915 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1920 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1921 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1922 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1923 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1924 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1926 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1927 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1929 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1930 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1932 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Football Rules Committee, minutes, 1933 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1871-1894 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1895-1902 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1903-1905 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1906 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1907 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1908 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1909 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1910 [A] (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1910 [B] (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1911 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1912 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1913 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1914 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1915 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1916 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1917-1919 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1920 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1922 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1923 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1924 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1925 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1926 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1927 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1928 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1929 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1930 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1933-1936 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1937-1940 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1941-1944 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1946 [A] (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1946 [B] (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1947 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1948 [A] (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1948 [B] (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1951 [A] (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1951 [B] (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1952 [A] (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1952 [B] (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1957-1958 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Football rules, questions concerning and interpretations of them, 1960-1963 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Changes in football rules, 1891-1941 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play - Blocking and Tackling (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Centering (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Choice of goal (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Downs (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Equipment (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Field (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Forward pass (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Fumbles (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Kickoff (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Line (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Men in motion (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Night games (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Numerals (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Officials (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Out of bounds (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Personal fouls (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Point after (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Punting (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Quarterback running (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Safety (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Scoring (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Shift plays (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Side line coaching (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Subsitution (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Termination of play (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - A.A. Stagg's summary of the effects of rules on play, Time out (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Football fatalities, 1931 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Football fatalities, 1932 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Football fatalities, 1933 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Football fatalities, 1934 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Football fatalities, 1935 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Football fatalities, 1938 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Football fatalities, 1939 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Football fatalities, 1940 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Football fatalities, 1941 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Football fatalities, 1945 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Football fatalities, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Football fatalities, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1887-1893 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1894 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1895 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1896 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, September-October 1896 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, November-December (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1897 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, September-October 1898 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, November 1898 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, December 1898 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, September-October 1899 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, November-December 1899 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, Penn game 1899 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1900 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1901 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, September-October 1902 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, November-December 1902 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1903 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1904 [A] (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1904 [B] (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1905 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, September-October 1906 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, November-December 1906 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1907 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1908 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1910-1921 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning football at the U. of C., other conference teams and non-conference teams, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Series IV: Athletics-General
  - Baseball clippings, 1893 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Baseball clippings, 1894 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Baseball clippings, 1895 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Baseball clippings, 1896 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Baseball clippings, 1897 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Baseball clippings, 1899 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Baseball clippings, 1900 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Baseball clippings, 1901 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Baseball clippings, 1902 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Baseball clippings, 1903 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Baseball clippings, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Baseball clippings, 1905 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Amherst (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Beloit (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Brown (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, California (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Cornell (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Georgetown (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Georgia (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Grinell (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Harvard (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Holy Cross (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Illinois (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Indiana (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Iowa (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Kansas (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Lake Forest (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Michigan (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Minnesota (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Northwestern (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Pennsylvania (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Purdue (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence re baseball games, Wisconsin (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Technical aspects of baseball, Batting cage (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Technical aspects of baseball, Bleachers (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Technical aspects of baseball, Community baseball (non-U. of C.) (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Technical aspects of baseball, Evaluation of players, U. of C. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Technical aspects of baseball, Evaluation of conference teams (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Technical aspects of baseball, National baseball tournament (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Technical aspects of baseball, Permission for U. of C. players to play summer baseball (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Technical aspects of baseball, Eligibility of professionals (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Technical aspects of baseball, Team reunions (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Technical aspects of baseball, Rules (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Technical aspects of baseball, A.A. Stagg's baseball theory (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Technical aspects of baseball, Tickets, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Technical aspects of baseball, Umpires (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - 1893 Baseball Tournament [World's Columbian Exposition] (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - 1911 baseball season write-up (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Baseball, U of C vs. Waseda, Japan, 1910 (Burlington Railroad) (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Baseball, 1910, U of C vs. Waseda, Japan, 1910 Gilbert Bliss (Faculty representative) (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Baseball, U of C vs. Waseda, Japan, 1910 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Baseball, 1910 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Baseball, U of C vs. Waseda, Japan, 1911 (Box 63, Folder 5-6)
  - Baseball, U of C vs. Waseda, Japan, 1915 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Baseball, U of C vs. Waseda, Japan, 1920 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Baseball, U of C vs. Waseda, Japan, 1921 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Baseball, U of C vs. Waseda, Japan, 1924 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Baseball, U of C vs. Waseda, Japan, 1925 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Baseball, U of C vs. Waseda, Japan, 1927 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Baseball, U of C vs. Waseda, Japan, 1930 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Baseball, U of C vs. Waseda, Japan, 1933 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Basketball, correspondence and articles, 1892-1900 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Basketball, correspondence and articles, 1901-1910 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Basketball, correspondence and articles, 1911-1920 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Basketball, correspondence and articles, 1921-1926 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Basketball, correspondence and articles, 1926-1929 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Basketball, correspondence and articles, 1930-1933 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - A.A. Stagg's diagrams and theories of basketball (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Interscholastic basketball, 1917 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Interscholastic basketball, 1920 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Interscholastic basketball, 1921 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Interscholastic basketball, 1922 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Interscholastic basketball, 1923 (Box 65, Folder 5)